## Jonathan Tybirk

+45 50 59 22 96



☑ jonathantybirk@gmail.com



2800 Kgs. Lyngby

in linkedin.com/in/jonathantybirk 🖊



github.com/jonathantybirk >



jonathantybirk.com ↗

### **Profile**

I'm studying BSc Artificial Intelligence and Data at the Technical University of Denmark with experience in full-stack development (TypeScript, React, PostgreSQL), data science and automation scripting in Python, and maintenance of C# codebases. I enjoy building projects, solving problems, and learning from hands-on experience.

I want to become technically stronger while learning what it takes to build and scale startups. I'm a quick learner with a broad set of skills and interests, ready to take on challenges and contribute wherever I can. I'm a social person who works well with others and gets deeply invested in the problems I'm working on.

### Education

BSc Artificial Intelligence and Data student, Technical University of Denmark September 2023 - current

- GPA: 11.1 / 12
- Taking extended courses in Algorithms and Data Structures
- 6th-place finisher in the Danish National Championship in AI 2024 under team name Powered by SmartFridge

# Experience

Mission Control Developer, Danish Student Association for Rocketry September 2024 - current

- Implementing unit testing and logging in a large C# codebase in a team
- Refactoring old code to follow sensible structure and design patterns

## Student Assistant, Copenhagen Applied Research A/S

April 2024 - current

• Implementing Python automation scripts for data collection and processing

## Teaching Assistant, Technical University of Denmark

January 2024 - current

- Teaching 120 students Computer Programming as Assistant Lecturer
- Helped convert the Statistics course textbook and exercises from **R** to **Python**

# **Projects**

Full-Stack Website (React, TypeScript, CSS, PostgreSQL)

July 2024 - current

- A dynamic self-deployed website to show off my projects
- Integrated frontend and database through Node.js with appropriate code structure
- Check it out at jonathantybirk.com ↗

Modelling of Membrane Degradation (NumPy, pandas, SciPy, scikit-learn) March 2024 - May 2024

- Paid contract work to data model for Aprisium Pte. Ltd., a Singapore-based environmental services start-up
- Extensive code documentation and data visualizations (Matplotlib)

#### **Self-Operating Computer (LangChain, OpenAI API)**

February 2024 - May 2024

- Program to visually perceive a computer screen, and navigate using mouse, keyboard, and GPT-4V reasoning
- Built with **Python** with robotic process automation start-up *Symbolik.ai*



**Technical skills** Python / PyTorch / LangChain C#/.NET TypeScript, React, HTML, CSS SQL / PostgreSQL Git, Markdown Google Cloud, AWS

### Languages

Danish, native English, fluent Spanish, beginner German, beginner

#### **Additional qualifications**

- Chairman of the student council for 250 students at Gymnastikhøjskolen i Ollerup. I improved efficiency by delegating responsibilities to small task groups.
- Certified personal trainer, having worked with regular people to promote health through exercise and nutrition without toxic self-criticism.
- Cultural insight from solobackpacking many times across Europe. I like working with international and diverse groups of people.
- 4-month army enlistment on Bornholm. This taught me to teamwork effectively even under stressful conditions.
- Experience performing music as guitarist and front singer - this has helped me get over a fear of public speaking.
- Great joke-teller according to my programming students!







